komfo.com 2017-02-27

# Privacy policy - Komfo

_Last Updated:  _ _May 1_ _, 2013_

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy describes the overall company Privacy Policy of Komfo Inc. (referred to as “Komfo”, “komfo.com”, “we”, “us”, “our”) and the services offered on the komfo.com website (referred to as “Services”, “Service”).

This Policy explains how your personal information is collected and  used by Komfo. This privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to the Komfo Web sites (“Sites”). This Policy does not apply to the collection of information through our Applications. To learn about how a Komfo customer uses the information it collects through our Applications, please see its privacy policy.

**Cookies**

We may automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive by a Web site. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve our Sites and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing our Sites, to personalize your experience, and to remember your preferences. We also use cookies in advertising and remarketing campaigns with Google adwords.

We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of our Sites. The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies to collect data in order to enable us to provide a better user experience.

**Personal Information**

We collect information from you in various ways when you use our Sites. We may collect personal information you directly provide on our Sites. Information we may collect includes name and email address, and phone number.

In addition, when you visit our Sites some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit including ours. That information includes your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your computer’s operating system and information about your usage and activity on our Sites. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user-base as a whole.

We use your personal information to provide you with services, to operate and improve our Sites , to send you messages, and for other purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Sites or in connection with our services.

We do not share your personal information with third parties like:

  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers (“Service Providers”) who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
  * to (a) comply with laws or respond to lawful requests and legal process, (b) to protect the rights and property of Komfo, our agents, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use, or (c) in the good faith belief that disclosure is needed to respond to an emergency or protect the personal safety of any person; and
  * in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. In any such event, we will provide notice if your data is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at privacy@komfo.com
